dallasmarketingservices.com 2019-06-01

# Privacy - Dallas Internet Marketing | Dallas SEO Company

Dallas Marketing Services is committed to protecting the privacy of the information that we collect from users of our Web site. Information is obtained through user-submitted request-for-more information forms. These forms require users to give us contact information (such as name, company, e-mail address, street address, telephone and fax numbers and educational information). This data is used to provide the information to those who inquire about our business and services offered or employment opportunities.

We consider your data to be private and confidential. We will not give, rent, loan, or sell any identifiable personal information to any other third party, unless legally required to do so. We may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services. In addition, we may use that information to contact you.

We use “cookies” on our Web Sites. Cookies are pieces of information or data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies tell our computer that you’ve visited before and can help to make your visit more personal so you don’t have to re-enter info on a return visit. Cookies also allow us to count the number of unique and return visitors who use our Web Sites.

Our website is protected with a variety of security measures. We employ a variety of mechanisms to ensure that data you provide is not lost, misused, or altered inappropriately.

Our Web site may contain links to Web sites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site before disclosing any personal information on that site.

If you have any questions about this Privacy policy statement, the practices of this website or your dealings with Dallas Marketing Services, contact us using the information in the contact section on the website. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting a new policy at this location.
